Today I want to talk about sales. I want
to talk about getting people to buy what
you offer. I mentor a group of coaches
and one of the problems that they come
up with to me is that they can get a lot
of leads using our system and what we
teach. They get a bunch of people who
show up with them, but once those leads
come in, they can't get them to buy from
them. And the reason why as I dig deeper
is because of a lack of skill when it
comes to getting the sale. It's a skill
that listen sales is not about you
convincing anybody to buy from you. It
is a way of imparting emotion to
somebody and belief in what you offer.
The reason why people buy from you is
because they trust that they are going
to get the result that you're talking
about. And it's big enough of a change
and a transformation for them.
That the pain of
leaving behind what they've been
experiencing
is less than staying in what they're
experiencing. And it actually turns into
pleasure. How many of you enjoy buying
things that you love? You actually feel
excitement and pleasure and joy. This is
what you want to get to when you're
selling. The problem is is that a lot of
people, they treat sales like pulling
teeth. And nobody wants their teeth
pulled. But what you want to do is you
want to create an experience in somebody
where they enjoy the process of getting
sales, okay? Of of being sold to. And
one of the reasons why I'm actually so
good at sales is because I don't take it
seriously very much. I don't try to be
the best salesperson. I just show up as
myself and I just connect with people
without worrying what are they going to
think about me? Is this going to produce
a result? The worst thing that you can
do when trying to get a sale is to try
to impress people. Is to try to get
people to like you. And by the way, not
everybody's going to like you. I
literally have people who watch my
videos, they watch my content, and they
think that I'm the dumbest box of rocks
that's out there. And and and that I
could never accomplish the things I talk
about. Partially because I don't have
the same cadence as other people. Um I
don't show up with the uh bravado
of a lot of sales trainers that are out
there. And yet I get incredible sales
closing ratios because when somebody
talks to me, I know how to show up with
that relaxed energy where it doesn't
feel like I'm trying to sell them, where
I'm not trying to get the sale. By the
way, every single piece of content that
I create is in that same type of energy.
And I don't I I am not trying to get a
sale in anything that I'm doing. I'm
just looking to connect and build trust
with the right person, with the person
who I want to connect with. Okay? And
so, first off, that's the first thing.
You got to build trust. They have to
believe in you, your product, your
service, your company, and the
transformation that you're promising.
Okay? And then they also have to realize
that not doing something right now, what
is doing something? Doing something is
purchasing what you offer. the offer
that you have for sale is an action that
they need to take in order to go from
point A to point B. And so really what
you're looking to do is to get them to
reframe
their view of what apathy and stagnation
means. So a lot of people they go in and
they don't want to be sold especially
when they are dealing with coaches or
mentors or trainers. They don't want to
be sold something, but they want a
solution to their problem. So that's
what you do is you give and promise
people a solution to their problem. And
then you go through the sequence of
actually building that trust and
imparting the belief, emotion, and logic
that you have about what you offer. If
everybody that you were selling to knows
what you know about your offer, they
would buy it from you. Okay? Unless
you're a scammer,
then they wouldn't, which is which is
not, you know, that's not what we do
around here at this channel is we're not
encouraging you to scam people at all.
Please do not do that. Um, don't watch
my channel. In fact, if that's what you
intend to do is to defraud people,
seriously, because the people who we
attract, the people who work with us,
they have integrity. And if you're
watching this right now, I believe that
you're a person of integrity. And that's
partially why we or you may struggle
with getting sales. If you're still
watching this video, you want to grow in
your ability to get sales. I I that's
just you wouldn't be listening to me
talk for the last five minutes if you
weren't wanting to get more sales or
increase your skill at sales. And so
with that, like you cannot let
the fear of judgment from other people,
the worry that they're not going to buy
from you get into your head. This is one
of the things that affects so many
people that I work with is that they get
so caught up in their head trying to get
people to buy from them, trying to get
the sale. when all you got to do is you
just got to build a connection with
somebody and then you got to go through
the sequence with them. Now, there's two
different types of sales. We're going to
talk about one-on-one sales in this
video. I want to talk about getting
somebody on the phone or talking to them
through direct message.
What you want to do is you want to learn
and discover and get them talking about
themselves. Get them talking about
individually what they
want, what their dreams, what their
desires are. As you grow and build your
business, you will notice patterns
across different people that you work
with. And then those patterns you bring
into every single message that you
offer. Every single video that I make
follows the patterns of what I know and
who I know I impact and who shows up in
my coaching programs. What they need,
what they desire. It's actually based
off of the conversations that I have
with my clients every single week. We
were just having a coaching call with
one of my clients on this exact topic
right here. And we had a great back and
forth conversation inside of my wealthy
coach academy program, which is the
premier coaching program that I have
where I help mentors, coaches, service
providers, trainers be able to get more
clients and know exactly what to say,
how to say it, when to say it, when to
show up to get more sales and what to do
with their advertising, their marketing,
their funnels, and all of that. We walk
you through that. I come alongside you
and guide you through that entire
process, not just with courses, but by
working with me. Okay? And so what you
have to do is you have to get to the
point where you realize that somebody
buying from you is a service
that you are doing them a service that
you are helping them that you are
helping them reach, achieve, and
experience something that they wouldn't
otherwise experience by not working with
you. Now, sure, they could go somewhere
else, buy from somebody else and
experience that. But why? Why? Why not
you? Why not now?
And I want you to get that in your mind.
Why not me? And why not now?
Oftentimes,
we're trying to be way too passive
and appease other people when we're
selling or in a sales interaction. I
don't want to be too pressuring. I don't
want them to feel like I'm I'm just in
it for the sale. Listen, like that
thought process right there is literally
getting in your way because you are
trying to impress somebody. You're
trying to control how they perceive you.
Instead, you just let it go.
Don't even try to get a sale. Don't even
try to just connect with somebody. But
be super confident in what you offer. Be
super excited about what you offer. the
last eight minutes of this video. That's
exactly the kind of energy that I'm
talking about when I say that I don't
give a
bleep about what you think about me
right now. You can think whatever you
want. I'm also confident in what I
offer. And I also know that this works.
And if you can carry that energy where
you just have fun with it and you just
have fun with the experience and you're
just connecting and talking for the sake
of connecting and talking with people,
but you also don't hide the fact that
you have something for sale. Like I
don't hide the fact that I do this that
I make these videos because of my
wealthy coach academy program that you
can check out the link in the
description below. I don't hide the fact
that I have an offer, that I offer
something to people that's going to
change their life and their business if
they jump in. I don't hide that. I don't
try to pretend like that doesn't exist.
I'm very upfront about it, very open
about it. And that's what you want to do
as well because that shows honesty, that
builds trust right there, right from the
get-go. And so then the process that you
want to do if you're talking one-on-one
with somebody, you can actually create a
customized
offer by listening to what their desires
are. There's actually a sequence. One of
my first jobs that I ever had, I was
working for a sales training company
where they actually taught people how to
sell products and services. And this was
in the network marketing industry. Not
necessarily my favorite industry
overall. I prefer what I do today. I
think it helps a lot more people
overall. Um though network marketing
does help people. Uh but
ultimately what they taught was how to
get people to buy from leads that you
got and what to get them what what
sequence to take people through to get
them to become a customer of yours to
buy a $500,000 program. And so the
sequence is you want to listen to listen
to what the desire of the person is. And
you also want to be the one asking the
questions. Ask the questions about
their family, what they like to do for
fun, what they do for work.
And usually if you just start a
conversation
casually, they're going to give you one,
two, or three of those things, and
they're going to start to talk about
them themselves. And then you can start
to unpack that. And then that builds
trust. But you want to guide it. Then
you don't want to spiral off into Pluto.
You want to guide it to
what your message is and you want to
guide it towards listening to what their
desires are. You want them to tell you
what they desire. What do they want more
than anything else? And then what you do
is you simply mirror their energy
and raise up their energy at the same
time. So this is what I like to do in a
sales conversation is I will mirror the
person's energy when I start and then I
will increase the my energy so that they
start mirroring my energy and
excitement. And then that imparts to
them what I'm feeling and my belief that
I have and what I offer. And then I
start mirroring and repeating back to
them what they told me their desires
were. And you can still do this through
webinars. You can still do this through
YouTube and and mass marketing as well.
When you listen to enough people what
their desires are, what their struggles
are, what their problems are, you can
mirror all of that in the sales copy, in
your messaging, in what you talk about,
in your offers, and all those different
ways that you reach people. If you're
doing a one-on-one conversation, you
literally repeat back to them. So,
listen. I know that you said that you
want to go on a vacation with your
family and that you're struggling by
having to work so many hours and having
to help your daughter who's in and out
of rehab. What if you could make a
lasting change in your life, your
family's life, and your future?
I know that by working with us, that
change will happen. And so, let's say
that that's what somebody told us that
they were dealing with. They were
dealing with a daughter who was in and
out of rehab. they were um wishing they
had enough time to go on vacation,
having the funds to be able to do so.
I'm able to repeat back to them some of
those things that they mentioned that
they want to do. And so what that does
is it and but when you do it truly
honestly like
you're not try listen you got to get it
out of your head trying to like get
people to like you trying to get them to
trust you trying to get them to believe
in you trying to control their
perception of you. You got to get this
out of your head because you're not
showing up real and authentically. You
show up like a robot. you show up as
somebody who's just like not even worth
listening to. Your your energy
reeks of desperation when you do that.
And so instead, if you can literally
just be yourself, casual, I'm talking
like the version of yourself that shows
up on Saturday watching football,
drinking a beer if that's what you like
to do. That version of you.
Seriously, like the version of you
that's sitting around at family dinner
talking to a long friend. That's the
version to show up with. The one that is
not trying to control the perception.
And maybe that's what you do in all your
conversations and and all of that. You
got to stop that if you want to learn to
get more sales. If you want to get more
people buying from you, be more
authentic. Just be yourself. Stop trying
to control what everybody thinks about
you, how they see you, how they perceive
you, and just start talking and
connecting
casually, way more casually. Stop trying
to be so professional,
be more casual, and you will affect far
more people in a positive way. I promise
you that. All right, listen. If you're a
mentor, if you're a coach, if you're a
trainer, and you want to get more
clients in your business, I'll show you
how to get more leads. I'll show you how
to get more sales in my Wealthy Coach
Academy program. Click one of the links
in the description of this YouTube video
and I'll see you in there. Talk soon.